export default {
  decks: [
    {
      title: "Nouns",
      uid: "Kk4Xj8-uvNmDyxe27wOo61Et9tjKeTbr",
      suid: "Kk4Xj8",
      cards: [
        {
          front: "table",
          back: "стол",
          lastReview: null,
          nextInterval: 86400000,
        },
        {
          front: "chair",
          back: "стул",
          lastReview: null,
          nextInterval: 86400000,
        },
        {
          front: "pencil",
          back: "карандаш",
          lastReview: null,
          nextInterval: 86400000,
        },
        {
          front: "cup",
          back: "чашка",
          lastReview: null,
          nextInterval: 86400000,
        },
        {
          front: "room",
          back: "комната",
          lastReview: null,
          nextInterval: 86400000,
        },
        {
          front: "door",
          back: "дверь",
          lastReview: null,
          nextInterval: 86400000,
        },
        {
          front: "window",
          back: "окно",
          lastReview: null,
          nextInterval: 86400000,
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      title: "Verbs",
      uid: "Qkj0Eq-79bvWkzzHvZV1qkxkKYcwadzS",
      suid: "Qkj0Eq",
      cards: [
        {
          front: "make",
          back: "делать",
          lastReview: null,
          nextInterval: 86400000,
        },
        {
          front: "work",
          back: "работать",
          lastReview: null,
          nextInterval: 86400000,
        },
        {
          front: "eat",
          back: "есть",
          lastReview: null,
          nextInterval: 86400000,
        },
        {
          front: "drink",
          back: "пить",
          lastReview: null,
          nextInterval: 86400000,
        },
        {
          front: "write",
          back: "писать",
          lastReview: null,
          nextInterval: 86400000,
        },
      ],
    },
  ],
};
